Support for NPR comes from Moises, the
creative suite for musicians used by
over 75 million artists worldwide to
learn, create, and collaborate.
Available for phone, tablet, and
desktop.
>> It's crazy.
[music] Yeah.
>> Heavenly Father, [music and singing]
why?
Heavenly Father, why you so far away?
>> Heavenly Father, why you so far away?
>> Yeah. [music]
Now, everybody telling me a lie.
[singing]
Now, Lord, they give me something for my
soul. See, I don't want to think of
[music] suicide, so please don't take
the lucky off my door. See, I was busy
loving all the girl [music] and I was
busy spinning [singing] on my door. And
if I get my story to the world, I wonder
if [music and singing] they put me for a
show. See, you can't handle pressure on
your own. So why you carry voter by
yourself? See, story [music] teller,
tell it wrong. They glorify [singing]
the horror in the web. Now [music] mama
call me, tell me, come me home. And I
just need some guidance in my steps. I
know I'm not the only one alone. I know
I'm not [singing and music] the only
one. I know I'm not the only one.
Heavenly Father, why you so far
[music] away?
Heavenly Father, why you so far? Yeah.
[music] Yeah. Yeah. Heavenly Father,
[singing] why you're so far away?
[music] Yeah.
And if I get my story to the world, I
wonder if they me. I wonder if they me
for Okay. Okay. Okay.
Thank y'all. [cheering]
[applause]
Yeah.
Well, look. See, [music] it's the same
[__] The rock, a pocket full of knots,
the peels, the blow, the yak, the top,
the drop, the [music] swerve, then pass,
the props, the safe, the stash, then
pad, the lock, the man,
[music and singing] the myth, the
legend, the great, the plan. Get money
till I'm dead. Perfecting my little
trap. They know me down [music] in chat
out in Memphis and Japan. I'm [singing]
running out of land. I feel like I could
fly. Just made 200 B. Just [music]
living how I live. I make this in my
crib. Just focus on my meals. My [music]
plate states, the grass, the fam, the p
the [music] cops harass is fast as hell.
From 12 to 12. The dash, [singing] the
chills. It's lace for real. [music] The
cake, the spill, the faith, the work,
the race, the wheels, the circle, the
bank. It's late, but still today, you
got to get off your ass and
[music and singing] live the base. It's
something like a crash,
>> but then I do my dance, but it's the
same [__]
[applause]
>> Tiny days, tiny dance.
We appreciate y'all for coming out.
Thank y'all for being such a great
audience and giving me the energy. We
got some more energy to give y'all. Um,
[music] we just started tour. So, we
want to thank y'all for I see
I see everybody in here. I see [music]
people actually singing these words back
to me. I ain't know what to expect. So,
I want to I want to thank y'all [music]
personally for making our last album,
The House is Burning, turned gold, last
week. You know what I'm saying? You know
what I mean? Um, what [music] else? The
Suns Tate also is officially gold. So,
if you are here for any of that, we
appreciate that type of I ain't going to
talk your head off too much. I got I'm
going to keep it I'mma keep it going.
So, ain't worry about me like that.
[music] All right. Oh, and thanks to my
amazing band while I'm already in, but
[applause and music]
banging through the night.
Yeah.
[music]
Are y'all ready? Yeah. [music]
Yeah. [singing]
Hey, [singing]
>> and I ain't never felt no type [music]
of way about this living do [singing] or
die.
>> Yeah. And
when they see our push,
>> they push me to the side.
>> Push [music and singing] me.
At least we fell in love with something
suicide. [music]
>> At [singing] least we
>> Do you feel good? Good.
>> How you feel?
>> Is it real love? Love. Uh-uh.
Do [music] you feel good? Good.
[singing] Good. Uh uh.
>> How you feel?
>> Is it real love? Love. Uh uh.
Yeah. See, see. [music] I travel, hey,
for you [singing] and you and you and
you and and I battle. [music]
>> Yeah. For [singing] for you.
>> For you. Yeah. Cuz I love
to call
your name. [music] Yeah. I travel. I I I
[singing] travel
>> for you and you and you. Hey. [music]
So, can we fall in love? I s play
banging through the night. [music]
And [singing] I ain't never felt no type
of way about [music] this living do or
die.
And [music] when they see our age, they
say we young, I let you push me to
[singing] the side.
At least [music] we fell [singing] in
love with something greater than
debating suicide.
[music] At least we fell in love.
Is it real?
Uh oh. Yeah.
Yeah. Uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh.
Hey, let me get the bass. Let me get the
bass. [music]
Yeah. Okay. All right. For sure. Let me
see. Um,
[music]
how we feeling? Let me get a um Let me
just get bass and keys. Bass and keys.
Yeah. All right. All right. For sure.
All right. [music] 1 2 1 2 3 and
uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
yeah. Okay, you caught me by [music]
surprise in my brand new whip.
>> Baby, beat me in the
trip. Baby, bring back [music] the up to
[singing] all his baby.
[music] Up to
hey. Who want to shot? Want to die? Let
me know. I got two in the hip and not no
dig. You smooth like a R&B song. How you
keep them hoes out your man? They
killing me. Uno. Might kick [__] like
judo. Giving out hoes now. Kudos
fat like Juno. You know. Hey, I tell a
chick eat it [music] like a cat. You see
the wrist whipping like border crest. I
got a [__] bigger than border piss and
the shots ain't bringing my soldier back
from the noose [music] to the drop in a
W. No digger. Be new to the top and the
rock. New Tiffany Z. You smooth like a
R&B
caught me by surprise
[singing]
me.
>> If it's cool to read [music] your mind
to read your mind,
baby, [music and singing]
>> if it's cool to read your mind. Oh, feel
good. A [__] been back but a [__] done
[music and singing]
change. We couldn't settle my fly.
Couldn't cover my
langu.
[singing]
[music]
Yeah.
[music and singing]
>> [__] Yeah.
[singing]
[music] See, I I I
I
>> [music]
>> Hey
hey
[music] I see see I cut my head b my
head and fell off top and run on sins
[music] in front of friend if we don't
win and pay your ties and me your fing
see [music] I cut my head above my head
and fell off top and run on sins in
front of friend if we don't win and pay
your ties and me your fins and we
[singing] all right with [music] big old
rims and LA homes if that ain't gone if
I ain't gone I ain't gone I ain't
>> [singing]
>> D. I ain't dumb. No more [music] ends
and no more trends in photo 10 and photo
lens. Notice this P [__] bonafide. Wo is
me bowl of grit. Naked pimp [music] beam
it up clean as [__] Other side. Chill
[singing] for [__] Making life look
clear for [__] Hill for [__] Tip
top cliff for [__] This the vision
[music] side to side. Some gifted [__]
If you honest, you going to miss a
[__] Twist it with them. This the ism.
Your [__] might kiss a [__] with a
[__] Get specific. A big ass pot. Rich
is missing. Your [music] shitty if it
isn't. [singing] This cost and scar your
face. The wrongs has caught a case of
[__] didn't mob like Carter say from
far away [music] all my [__] like calm
down forever reason just can't find it
like a dozen people catch that vibe when
to get too tired to write dodge prison
it felt like
feel tonight [music]
feel like
Hey, [music] hey, baby, come [singing]
inside.
I [music] want to play some f [__]
>> And if you have [music] the time,
>> And if you [singing] have the time,
>> maybe you can slide [music] with me.
>> Slide. See, baby, stay tonight.
[music]
>> And I could be your boyfriend.
[music] And if that doesn't work,
then I just back [music] and forth late
night beside you. I don't know [singing]
no pain. I'm here kissing the back and
[music] forth late night beside you. I
[singing] don't know.
Here
my love. Really want my love.
[singing and music]
>> Do you want my love? Really want my
love. [singing]
Late [music] night beside you. I don't
know no pain. I'm here kissing no.
[singing]
[music] Hey baby, come inside.
I want to pacify [music]
[singing] you.
[music]
And maybe you can. Yeah. [cheering]
>> [music and applause]
>> Okay. Yeah.
On a mission, but it's [music] Hey, see
I'm the man on the mission, but it's
taking me back and forth. Man, [music]
on the mission, but it's
duh. My mama don't want no drugs up in
this house. Hide the [music] dust. I'm
never saying off this love. And when you
doubt, it's like a flush. That baby
don't know the price to hit these
heights. Don't you touch my mama
screaming [music] jump
>> jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump
jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump
jump jump jump jump jump
>> high I'm fried can you order some fries
for me can you spot a lie [music] when
the government tied to it beat for your
eye then they [__] [singing] your
mind to get a beat at the lie got me up
in the fire [__] [music] we got a blind
them people despise it here please give
me time we ticking the bomb the d come
alive now we doing the line [music]
again they waiting outside you must be
read my mind I'm the man on the mission
but it's taking [music] me
Man on the mission, but it's taking me
on a mission, but it's taking me back.
[music] Man on a mission, but it's hey,
I'm the man on the mission, but it's
taking me back. Man on the mission, but
it's
[music]
[cheering]
[applause]
[music]
[__] right. [__] right. Yeah.
Yeah.
Uh uh [music]
uh uh uh [music and singing] uh uh. Hey,
I hate lights in the ceiling. Can we lay
[music and singing] outside? Lights in
the ceiling. Can we stay outside? Going.
You a jerk and you've been way [singing]
outside. Hey, see baby. I hate lights
[music] in the ceiling. Can we lay
outside? Lights in the ceiling. Can we
stay outside? Going. You a junkie. You
been way outside. Hey, just
>> just focus. [music]
>> Just focus.
>> Just focus. [singing]
Just focus. Just [music] Hey, see
Bailey, I'm worth more than [singing] my
rap [__] Hey, worth more [music] than
my rap [__] Hey, getting caught in the
rapture. Hey, getting caught in. Hey,
Bailey, [music and singing] I need more
than my last one. Hey, I need more than
attachments. Hey, I need more [music]
than the best work. Hey, these war
interactions, baby, I ain't dead [music]
yet amongst them. Hey, I ain't dead, but
my cup dirt. Hey, I ain't scared of you,
but but I'm scared of your love. Like,
baby, [music] life ain't fair. Do your
heart work. Hey, cuz I'm nailed to the
artwork. Hey, don't stare at a Wait,
[music] wait. See, don't stare at a
heartbreak, baby. I hate life in the
ceiling. Can we lay [music] outside?
Lights in the ceiling. Can we stay
outside? Where you going? You a You been
way outside. Hey, see baby I hate lights
in the ceiling. Can we lay outside?
Lights in the ceiling. Can we stay
[music] outside you and you wait
just focus just focus just focus.
[music]
Just focus. Just Hey. Hey. Just [music]
focus. Just focus. [singing] Just focus.
Just Hey.
Hey. I've been falling since August and
off the coffin you piece by piece the
piece be back. [singing]
I've been falling since August. Awful.
Often off the coffin you piece by piece
to piece [music] me back is torture
[singing] ch.
[music]
>> Hey, we work to [singing] work. You late
to work. I holler and they send it. You
know my plot was colder than Chicago
[music]
in December. My chick came up and angle
with her mama was her daddy. And when
I'm in the Midwest, she say holl at your
family. My dog pay [music and singing]
me that cup. It taste like candy. My dog
been laying on the laws and breaking on
the laws. I serving all the rock
southside. [music] Still [__] in the
car. Still flipping in the car. Still
shooting out the cart. Little hot
smoking out the jar with a star. [music]
Wait, them [__] say that I'm a cool
cat. [__] that. Tell them [__] I'm a
top dog. Get shot brother when I let a
propane outside. Bunch of [__] doing
[music] donuts. Yeah, got the money in a
headline. Big dog every time I hit the
red lights. Just shine. Ain't [music]
nothing but a good day. Don't die. Don't
teach matter. Wait. I ain't tripping. I
don't want to lose count. Talking my
[__] It was just [__] it. I'll drive.
Hop in my ride. P me that Dutch. We're
on [music] the west side on the 110.
Swinging mine. Swinging mine. Well, [__]
it. [singing] Let's build [__] less.
Spin a few crumbs. Pop smoke [music] pop
[__] pop this young [__] don't pop too
much spacious f Kanye [music] young
[__] don't stay too g big truck big
wheel big rock them [__] [music]
probably hate my guts trying to gain my
trust but it's all out [music]
[cheering]
[applause]
[music]
I like this next one I like this
I like [music] this is like a bunch of
affirmations
and realities at one time. I like to
slide. [music]
[singing]
>> Yeah. Yeah. I [music] got it jumping
like water. Part of boo. Hit the rain.
Baby, don't you spill all this [__]
It's contagious. Slide [music] through.
Then I dip. All these chips on my brain.
Plotting in my D on my hip like a
patient. [music]
Going through my phases. I've been
changing [singing] for the greater.
Three, four, five M later. [music] We
had a meeting in the kitchen. Bought
some chicken, some gravy. I'm right back
on the road. I know it pains me. See,
baby, what you [music] working on? I've
been working hard. [__] talking about
me bad. I done heard it all. [__] her
and her and him. [__] on your mama.
[music] Running from the law. Got free
my mind some time. I won't get high, but
I don't want my water. When I feel like
I can't breathe, I grab my blunt then my
flaw. I've been smoking to the island
all night long [music] in my car. I was
tripping. I got so drunk. I called my
mom. Man, she say I gota
[music]
[singing and music]
>> Hey, where you going? Come back to me.
Come back to me.
>> Where you going? [music]
>> Hey, where you going? [singing]
>> I want to get you. I want to get to know
you, baby. [singing] Where you going?
>> Hey, where you going?
>> Back and forth.
>> Hey, I want to get to know you.
>> I [singing] want to get to know you. The
heart got a mind of his song. Baby love,
[music] I'm sorry I ain't treat you like
the star that you was. Hey baby.
>> Hey baby.
>> The dream be making it hard to stay
baby.
>> Like in a perfect world would I trade
places [music] with you on stage? Watch
you do your dance. I'd be your number
one fan. If I had a chance, drove for a
day and a half for a photograph and
prayed. When I started to leave, you
were stopping.
Ask
me
[applause and music]
how you feel. Y'all feel like?
>> Y'all feel like?
>> If I could, [music]
if I could
one, two, one, two. If I could [music]
pay my
>> I'm coming over. Found a message in my
bottle. Your son is coming up.
[singing]
[music]
>> Well, y'all is saying you ain't nothing
but a baby. Your deal is growing up.
Listen.
And what you [music] call it was heaven
at the bottom and peace from throwing up
bottom.
>> But y'all [music and singing] is saying
you ain't nothing but a baby. Your is
growing. I think I do this [__] for real
dog.
>> I [music] ain't no [__] maybe.
I'm for [__] real dog.
>> Well, mama [singing] mama [music] I got
some dollars for your bills dog.
>> Bills.
>> Now I'm the head and I'm the topic. All
it [music] matters. I'm J. [singing]
Hey.
Well, you know [music] I think the
sunshine should should feel [singing]
how I feel and how I feel [music] like.
Yeah. I think at night time the the moon
should call my phone. Just
[music and singing] hit my line. I'm
here for you.
Like shame on earth. My rain. [music]
Come on down. [singing]
>> I figure the moon. I figure I figure
[music] that when I pay my bills I'm I'm
coming over. Found a message in my
bottle. Your son is coming up [music]
louder. [singing]
>> What y'all are saying? You ain't nothing
but a baby. [music] Your fear is growing
up. Listen. [singing]
>> And what you call it was heaven at the
bottom and peace from throwing [music]
up. [singing]
>> What y'all are saying? You ain't nothing
but a baby. Your deal is growing up
paid.
Hey, [music] you ain't nothing but a
baby. Your deal is growing up. Hey,
tiny dance. Tiny dance. [cheering]
Tiny.
I like to thank y'all. I want to thank
y'all for praying for me. I I've I've um
every message and you know what I'm
saying, every reach out. I've I've I've
received it and I appreciate [music] it.
So, I want y'all to know I'm praying for
y'all, too. So before we get out of
here, I got a little prayer for you if
you would listen to me. You know what
I'm saying? [music]
If I had my [__] heart broke,
is it that hard to believe? [singing]
Cuz I've been banging [music] out the
[singing] inside
and working hard for the weave.
[music] Cuz baby used to be [singing] my
best friend.
It's some good info.
Cuz baby used to be my
[music and singing] best friend.
It's good in fo
[singing]
>> if I had my [__] heart broke.
[singing and music]
>> Is it that hard to believe?
>> Cuz I've been banging out the inside
[singing]
and working hard for the we.
>> Yeah, [singing]
>> cuz baby used to be my best friend.
and some good info [singing]
>> Hey, y'all [singing] mind y'all might
[music] help me out with this one? Y'all
help me
through.
If I had my [__] heart,
>> but had my [__] [music] heart
broke.
>> Is it that hard to believe?
>> Is it that hard to believe? [singing]
Yeah. Yeah.
>> Cuz I've been banging out the inside.
Cuz [music] I've been banging out the
inside.
>> Working hard for the week.
>> I've been working hard [singing] for the
Wii. Yeah. [music] Yeah.
>> Baby used to be my best friend.
[singing]
>> Some good info.
>> It's some good info.
>> This baby used to be my best friend.
>> This baby used to be [music] my some
good info.
>> Hey yo, Tiny Des. Thank y'all for having
me. [music] Shout out to my label, my
managers, my brothers, my producers.
We'll see y'all next time. Thank you.
Love
[music]
[applause]
[cheering]
you.
[applause]
Thanks so much for watching. Support for
NPR Music comes from Moises, committed
to ethical innovation and empowering the
creative community with tools for
musicians to master their craft. A quick
update before you go, we're doing
another Tiny Desk giveaway. Enter by
September 12th, 2026, and you and a
friend could win a free trip to DC to
see a Tiny Desk concert live [music] in
person. You even get to choose which
upcoming show you want to see, and it's
completely free to enter. Just go to
npr.org/tinyes
giveaway. Entering is completely free,
but you can get more entries by snagging
some limited edition Tiny merch or by
making a special donation to the NPR
network. Learn more and enter today at
npr.org/tinyes
giveaway.